<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:createdBy="admin"
    jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
    courseArea="Tour and Travel Services"
    courseContent="Convey positive attitude to guests&#xa;- Take action to minimize guests dissatisfaction&#xa;- Report or document concerns&quot;"
    courseCost="25"
    courseDetails="Course updated January 1st, 2016!&#xa;&#xa;Note: Tim Buchalka, the course instructor for this Java course got voted in the top 10 BEST instructors for Udemy in late December 2015, as voted by students in the course!&#xa;&#xa;This is out of a total of 18,000 instructors!&#xa;&#xa;&#xa;&#xa;&#xa;Frustrated trying to learn how to program?&#xa;&#xa;My name is Tim Buchalka and I'd like to ask you to come with me on a journey as I take you from a beginner to an experienced Java developer!&#xa;&#xa;Over 33,000 students are already enrolled in my other programming courses and have left hundreds of five star reviews.&#xa;&#xa;Why?&#xa;&#xa;Because I've taught them how to program successfully and made learning fun at the same time.&#xa;&#xa;Now its your turn! Are you ready to learn how to program?&#xa;&#xa;This course assumes no previous experience, and takes you from the absolute beginner concepts like showing you the tools you need to download and install, writing you very first Java program, and then goes into more detail as we explore the entire Java feature set.&#xa;&#xa;All the basic Java keywords, operators, statements, and expressions are explained in great detail, together with complete chapters on object oriented programming and the Java API.&#xa;&#xa;You learn to develop powerful Java applications using one of the most powerful Integrated Development Environments on the market, IntelliJ IDEA!&#xa;&#xa;Read all the 5 star reviews other students have left about this course!&#xa;&#xa;Now don't worry if none of that made any sense. Because, I go into great detail explaining each and every core concept, programming terms, and buzzwords.&#xa;&#xa;By the end of this course you will have a mastery of programming in Java no matter what level of experience you are at right now.&#xa;&#xa;Be sure to click the free preview button on this page if you want to get a taste of the quality of the training.&#xa;&#xa;My goal is not just to show you how to program, but to help you understand what you are doing, and why you are doing it as well!&#xa;&#xa;Not only do the videos show you how to become a programmer in great detail, but this course has a unique challenge feature included.&#xa;&#xa;Each time a core concept is taught, a video presents a challenge for you that is designed to help you really understand what you have just learned.&#xa;&#xa;You will go away and complete the challenge, and then come back and see the challenge answered and explained in detail in the video, allowing you to check your results!&#xa;&#xa;This is a fantastic way to really help you understand Java faster and ensure you will reach your goal of becoming a Java Developer in record time.&#xa;&#xa;As your instructor, I have over 30 years experience as a software developer and teacher, and have been using Java since around the year 2000. Yes, over 15 years!&#xa;&#xa;I am an expert programmer but also have the relatively unique ability to make teaching fun and easy.&#xa;&#xa;Don't worry, I might be a geek, but I do make programming fun and painless for you to learn!&#xa;&#xa;Not convinced? Just go and take a read of some of the rave reviews given to me on my other courses.&#xa;&#xa;The facts are that students love my courses and style of teaching, because it helps them reach their goals faster.&#xa;&#xa;Are you ready to let me help you become a Java developer?&#xa;&#xa;Course updates&#xa;&#xa;One of the things I pride myself on is how often I add new content to my videos, and also how often I update them, and this course is the same.&#xa;&#xa;As an example, my Android course has had over 20 hours of material and numerous updates applied to it to ensure its current and is of the best quality for you.&#xa;&#xa;I'll be constantly adding new material to the course as well as updating it on a regular basis to make sure you access to the best and most update to date and comprehensive Java training available!&#xa;&#xa;Here is a list of the content being added on a regular basis!&#xa;&#xa;As i mentioned in the very first video in the course, there is a lot of new content to come!&#xa;&#xa;Finish off Encapsulation and challenge exercises and then Polymorphism and challenge exercises.&#xa;&#xa;Arrays, Java's inbuilt Lists, Autoboxing and Unboxing&#xa;&#xa;What arrays are, using int, String and other primitive types in Arrays, creating arrays of objects and exploring Java's inbuilt List classes. We finish off with Autoboxing and Unboxing.&#xa;&#xa;Section 10 – Naming conventions, Packages, static and final&#xa;&#xa;Get a deeper understanding of naming conventions, scope, packages. Plus we will discuss the static and final keywords.&#xa;&#xa;Section 11 – Inner And Abstract Classes &amp; Interfaces&#xa;&#xa;Learn to fully utilize inner and abstract classes, and also what makes interface different from classes.&#xa;&#xa;Inner Classes&#xa;&#xa;Abstract Classes&#xa;&#xa;Interfaces&#xa;&#xa;Section 12 – Generics&#xa;&#xa;What generics are and how to use them in your Java programs.&#xa;&#xa;Section 13 – Testing and Documentation&#xa;&#xa;How to test and debug Java program, exceptions and documentation.&#xa;&#xa;Debugging&#xa;&#xa;How to use the Java documentation to get the information you need.&#xa;&#xa;Setting up Java source code for analysis in IntelliJ&#xa;&#xa;Reviewing Java's own source code&#xa;&#xa;Exceptions&#xa;&#xa;Section 14 – Collections&#xa;&#xa;Have an understanding on the collections java framework, when to implement linkedlist or arraylist, difference between enummap and hashmap, as well as Enumset and Hashset.&#xa;&#xa;List, ArrayList and LinkedList&#xa;&#xa;Map, HashMap and EnumMap&#xa;&#xa;Set, EnumSet and HashSet&#xa;&#xa;Enums&#xa;&#xa;EnumMap&#xa;&#xa;Section 15 - Exploring Java's libraries&#xa;&#xa;Section 16 – Basic Input and Output&#xa;&#xa;Section 17 – Exploring java dot util dot *&#xa;&#xa;Section 18 – Concurrency&#xa;&#xa;Section 19 – Regular Expressions&#xa;&#xa;Section 20 – Lambda Expressions&#xa;&#xa;Section 21 – Extras&#xa;&#xa;This is the number one course you need to get enrolled in if you truly want to learn how to become a Java Developer.&#xa;&#xa;So, are you ready to get started? Enroll now and I look forward to seeing you inside!&#xa;&#xa;What are the requirements?&#xa;&#xa;A computer - Windows, Mac and Linux are all supported and setup and installation videos for each platform are included!&#xa;Nothing else is needed, everything you need to get started programming in Java is included in the course, and all the tools used are free.&#xa;What am I going to get from this course?&#xa;&#xa;Over 134 lectures and 26.5 hours of content!&#xa;Program fluently in Java&#xa;Understand the concepts of Object Oriented Programming&#xa;Be able to download and install Java on their computer&#xa;Understand Java Keywords, Expressions, Operators and Statements&#xa;Create their own java programs&#xa;Take their knowledge of Java to write applications for Android devices, the web, or even desktop applications&#xa;What is the target audience?&#xa;&#xa;The course is aimed at complete beginners and intermediate programmers. No previous programming experience is assumed!&#xa;If you are an expert Java program with extensive knowledge and many years experience, you may not get a lot out of this course. For everyone else the course is perfect for you!"
    courseHours="7"
    courseImageUrl="https://udemy-images.udemy.com/course/750x422/533682_c10c_2.jpg"
    courseLang="English"
    courseObjective="This course aims to provide people seeking employment in the F&amp;B (Retail) and Tourism industry with the skills and knowledge required to interact with guests in a retail store or food establishment."
    courseRef="CRS-Q-0002405-FB"
    courseTitle="INTERACT WITH GUESTS"
    courseType="WSQ"
    courseUrl=""
    status="approved"/>
